AZIM AKMATOV

Front-end developer

CONTACT

- +996 500 512 611
- azim.akmatov1@gmail.com
- Kyrgyzstan, Tokmok, Rovnyagin 120
- akmatoff.com

EDUCATION

IUCA College

2018-2021 Information Technologies Associate's Degree

SKILLS

TypeScript - React - Next.js -Angular

LANGUAGES

Kyrgyz (Native), Russian (C1), English (B2)

PASSIONS

- Guitar playing and singing
- Making electronic music

PROFILE

I am a front-end developer with 2 years commercial experience in front-end development. Worked with partners like Binance, Gcash, Vodapay, Touch'N'Go using technologies like Alipay's Mini Program Development Platform and Angular. Contributed to e-commerce platform Shopboxo using React and Next.js.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER INTERN

Appboxo

February 2022 - May 2022

Gain experience in web development and team work

- Troubleshooted and resolved client issues reported by support team within 48 hours
- Supported teammates in resolving bugs so they are more focused on delivering features
- Supported miniapps to function properly by resolving issues and delivering customizations requested by clients
- Take part in meetings and discussions with our partners and clients to sucessfully resolve issues and deliver custom features

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Appboxo

June 2022 - February 2024

Support miniapps and our e-commerce platform on buyer and seller sides

- Deliver new features and customizations for miniapps using Angular and Alipay's Mini Program Framework
- Support new merchants and partners like Binance, Gcash, Touch'N'Go, Vodapay
- Increase code quality by maintaining and refactoring old code
- Covering our e-commerce platform with E2E tests using Playwright